livemercial.com 2011-09-26

# Livemercial™

Effective Date: January 1, 2010  
By visiting this website or agreeing to receive e-mail marketing material from Livemercial Network, as defined below, you agree to be bound by the terms of the foregoing privacy policy and agreement (“Privacy Policy”). 

**Livemercial Network Respects Your Privacy**  
Livemercial Network, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company, its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively referred to as: "Livemercial Network", “we”, “our” or “us”) respect and value your privacy. As such, this Privacy Policy details Livemercial Network’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“PII”) that it collects when you provide PII directly to Livemercial Network through this website, e-mail or other electronic communication. This Privacy Policy also applies to consumers that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing material from Livemercial Network’s partner websites, third party partner websites, or otherwise (known as "List Management Arrangements").

Livemercial Network reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this website and the effective date of the policy will be modified to reflect the effective date of the most recent version. If a material change to our PII information practices occurs in the future, we will only use PII collected from the time of the policy change forward for these new purposes unless we have your consent.  

**Types of Information We Collect or Maintain About Consumers**  

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
PII is information that allows Livemercial Network to identify and communicate with an individual consumer. Through the use of this website and through the election to receive e-mail on third-party sites in List Management Arrangements with Livemercial Network, Livemercial Network may collect or maintain the following PII about consumers: 

   •First and Last Name  
   •Physical Address  
   •Email Address  
   •Phone Number  
   •Fax Number  
   •Any other PII the user submits during the course of normal correspondence with Livemercial Network, or its third-party companies

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
Non-personally identifiable information is information collected by Livemercial Network in the normal course of operating its business that does not reveal the specific identity of the consumer. This data records an individual’s activity either on the Livemercial Network website or within a Livemercial Network -initiated e-mail. Types of non-personally identifiable information collected include: 

   •IP Address  
   •Consumer click-stream data  
   •Consumer email-open data  
   •Aggregate click-stream data provided to Livemercial Network by third-party companies

**Children's Privacy**

Livemercial Network places the highest value on the privacy of children. Livemercial Network does not knowingly accept PII from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18, you may not use this website or receive e-mail marketing materials without the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**How We Use Consumer PII**

**Consumer PII collected on this site.**  
Livemercial Network will use consumer PII collected on this site to contact the consumer in response to consumer-initiated inquiries, to provide services requested by the consumer, to alert consumers to changes in services or features, and to provide consumers with requested information regarding Livemercial Network or our services. Livemercial Network may share this PII with service providers who assist us with our marketing efforts, but those service providers will not use this PII for their own marketing purposes and are prohibited by contract from sharing this PII with any party other than Livemercial Network. These businesses may include, but are not limited to: providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation services.

Livemercial Network may use data-enhancement providers to augment data provided to us by consumers on this site. Data-enhancement providers will not use the data for any purpose other than to provide the enhancement information to Livemercial Network, and are prohibited by contract from sharing that PII with any party other than Livemercial Network. Livemercial Network may, in order to provide the highest level of service, use data collected through another Livemercial Network property to enhance the data we collect on this site.

Livemercial Network may also share PII in the following limited circumstances: (1) upon receipt of a properly authorized and authenticated governmental request for information; (2) in response to a subpoena or a court order, (3) to comply with relevant laws; (4) in response to an investigation of fraud regarding a specific consumer, or (5) in an effort to safeguard the person or property of a Livemercial Network employee or a third party.

Finally, Livemercial Network may, in the future, decide to sell, merge or otherwise reorganize its business. Livemercial Network reserves the right to transfer and disclose PII in this circumstance, but data collected by Livemercial Network will be governed by the same privacy policy that existed prior to any change in business conditions unless you consent to the new privacy policy.

**Consumer information managed by Livemercial Network pursuant to a List Management Arrangement.**  
Livemercial Network is in the business of managing email-recipient lists for clients. As such, Livemercial Network receives PII from marketing partners and uses that PII to send relevant marketing content to those recipients. Livemercial Network’s use of PII collected by third-party marketing partners is limited to the uses allowed under the third-party's privacy policy previously agreed to by the consumer. Livemercial Network will utilize service providers who assist us with our marketing efforts, but those service providers will not use any PII collected by third-party marketing partners and managed by Livemercial Network for their own marketing purposes and are prohibited by contract from sharing that PII with any party other than Livemercial Network. These businesses may include, but are not limited to: providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation services.

Livemercial Network may, in order to provide the highest level of service, use data collected through another Livemercial Network property to enhance the data we manage for third parties.

Livemercial Network will share PII collected by third-party marketing partners and managed by Livemercial Network in the following limited circumstances: (1) upon receipt of a properly authorized and authenticated governmental request for information; (2) in response to a subpoena or a court order, (3) to comply with relevant laws; (4) in response to an investigation of fraud regarding a specific consumer, (4) if Livemercial Network is sold or acquired, or (5) in an effort to safeguard the person or property of a Livemercial Network employee or a third party.

Livemercial Network may, in the future, decide to sell, merge or otherwise reorganize its business. Livemercial Network reserves the right to transfer and disclose PII in this circumstance, but data collected by Livemercial Network will be governed by the same privacy policy that existed prior to any change in business conditions unless you consent to the new privacy policy.

**European Union Residents**  
Livemercial Network has self certified to the Department of Commerce’s Safe-Harbor framework and we adhere to the Safe-Harbor Principles. For more information on the Safe-Harbor program, visit <http://export.gov/safeharbor>. If you are a European resident and have a data-privacy inquiry, you may contact us at [info@asseenontvnetwork.com](mailto:info@asseenontvnetwork.com) or in writing at:

**Livemercial Network P.O. Box 1312, Valparaiso, IN 46384**

If your data privacy inquiry was not satisfactorily resolved by us then you may contact the DMA Safe Harbor Program at:

Safe Harbor Line  
Direct Marketing Association  
1615 L Street, NW - Suite 1100  
Washington, DC 20036  
Fax: 202-955-0085  
Telephone: 202-861-2410  
Email: [safeharbor@the-dma.org](mailto:safeharbor@the-dma.org)

For PII collected from consumers inside the European Union, Livemercial Network will not manage that consumer data unless that consumer first requested, pursuant to clear and conspicuous notice, to receive such types of marketing communications. Moreover, the EU recipient must be given clear and conspicuous notice that the data is going to be shared with third parties for marketing purposes, and that notice must be given prior to receipt of the recipient's permission.

**Choice**  
Livemercial Network manages e-mail lists through its List Management Arrangements. Consumers may wish to remove themselves from specific Livemercial Network marketing lists. As such, users may remove themselves from a specific mailing list by utilizing the list-unsubscribe option that is present and available at the end of each e-mail that Livemercial Network sends.

Moreover, consumers may elect not to receive advertisements from a specific advertiser at any time. In every e-mail communication we send, there is also an unsubscribe hyperlink that allows the recipient to unsubscribe from receiving commercial emails from that specific advertiser by clicking the hyperlink provided and following the instructions provided. We process all unsubscribe requests in a prompt fashion.

Unsubscribe requests are either processed on an advertiser-specific basis or on a list-specific basis, depending on the selection the consumer makes. Unsubscribing from one list managed by Livemercial Network will not remove the consumer from all Livemercial Network marketing lists. Similarly, unsubscribing from one advertiser will not prevent the consumer from receiving all advertisers' emails.

To unsubscribe from Livemercial Network, [click here](http://optout.vresp.com/do_opt_out.html?uid=7dd90b0204). 

**Cookies**  
Livemercial Network may employ "cookies" to help customize your access to the website, and for the delivery of targeted advertisements. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at our website and to facilitate the receipt of targeted advertisements.

We use cookies to track, monitor and target the interests of our users to further enhance the experience on our website, and for subsequent advertising and/or delivery purposes. To find out more about cookies, please visit <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>. To disable and reject cookies generally, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

In addition, for the purpose of formatting and delivering future campaigns, Livemercial Network may employ pixel tags (also known as clear gifs) to track: 1) the pages that our users visit on affiliate and/or partner websites; and 2) user opens of, and clicks on, our targeted email advertising. We reserve the right to employ user source information, including applicable category and interest(s), for the marketing of targeted e-mail messages. This source information may be shared with our third party marketing partners. Livemercial Network reserves the right to retain cookie and pixel tag data indefinitely

**Livemercial Network’s third party cookie services**

**Use of Cookies  **  
We deploy both first-party and third-party cookies when consumers open and “click” a link within the emails we send pursuant to our list-management relationships or when consumers register on a partner site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing activity-based information about you, and it is designed to facilitate the receipt of targeted and relevant advertisements. The cookie is not associated with your email address or any other PII. 

Livemercial Network’s cookies are used to for two purposes. First, Livemercial Network leverages cookies to better serve display advertising to consumers; these advertisements are chosen to meet specific consumers previous web-surfing or demographic data, but the advertisements are not selected using data such as WHO specifically a consumer is. Secondly, Livemercial Network leverages cookies to provide partners with demographic information regarding the consumers who visit the partner’s site. Again, no PII(such as name or email address) is included in the cookies Livemercial Network sets. 

To find out more about cookies generally, please visit <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>. Should you wish to opt-out of us placing a marketing cookie on your browser, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Additionally, every email we send as a result of a list management relationship contains a bit of code known as a “web beacon.” This code allows us to understand the time and date of when a user has opened an email and when he/she has utilized a link within the email to visit a Web site. Our web beacons do not collect PII. Users wishing to disable our web beacons should do so by turning images “off” in their email client (e.g., Outlook, Outlook Express). Please see your email client for more information.

**Group Aggregate Data**

Livemercial Network reserves the right to provide aggregate or group data about Livemercial Network users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage, or characteristics of Livemercial Network participants as a group, without disclosing PII.

**Right to Contact Via Telephone**

In addition, by registering at the website, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the "Rule"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, we reserve the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule.

**Security**

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users' information. When users submit information at the website or when our third-party marketing partners transfer PII to us, such information is protected both online and offline. The servers in which we store PII are kept in a secure physical environment. Livemercial Network has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. Currently, Livemercial Network uses Secure Socket Layer Software ("SSL") to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, names and addresses as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although we take reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, Livemercial Network cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our website is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.

**Access**

Consumers wishing to review PII collected by Livemercial Network on this site should write to Livemercial Network Privacy Department, Livemercial Network P.O. Box 1312 Valparaiso, IN 46384. Livemercial Network may take reasonable steps to confirm the identity of the consumer in an effort to prevent identity theft.

Consumers wishing to review PII list managed by Livemercial Network but collected on a third-party site pursuant to the third-party's privacy policy should contact the third-party company responsible for the collection of the consumer's PII.

**You’re California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have provided PII to Livemercial Network or its partners in list management arrangements to request certain information regarding Livemercial Network’s disclosure of PII to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Within thirty days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of PII disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this section.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@asseenontvnetwork.com](mailto:info@asseenontvnetwork.com) or in writing at:

Livemercial Network   
Customer Service Department  
P.O. Box 1312  
Valparaiso, IN 46384
